cash4offers.com 2006-06-16

# The Cash4Offers.com Privacy Policy

**The Cash4Offers.com Privacy Policy  
_(Last updated December 20, 2005)_**

The Cash4Offers.com has developed the web technology to enable businesses to interact with consumers in highly personalized ways without forfeiting the privacy of the consumer. Privacy is a critical element of The Cash4Offers.com. Our Privacy Policy is an evolving document and as such will be updated periodically. We welcome feedback about the guidelines outlined in our policy. 

  1. The Cash4Offers.com will control all information collected as a result of your membership in The Cash4Offers.com. We do not give, sell, rent, share, or trade any identifiable personal information regarding our members to any third party, with the exception of third-party advertisers who work with The Cash4Offers.com to provide our subscribed members with occasional, targeted advertisements through the site's Direct Mail system or as outlined elsewhere in this document.

  2. In our online registration form, we require you to provide us with certain personal information about yourself including full name, address, e-mail address, and phone number. We then require that our members complete a short demographic profile. We will process this information to administer your membership and to enable you to take advantage of other member benefits. We will process this membership and demographic information to build a profile of your interests and activities so that our advertisers can send you advertisements, offers and other benefits that are most likely to be of interest to you. As we aggregate this type of information about all of our members, we offer summaries to our advertisers and other interested parties so that they can learn what products and services are most popular to consumers, but we do not disclose our members' names, addresses, e-mail addresses, phone numbers, or other personally identifiable information to these third parties.

  3. We may ask you for personal information at other times, including, but not limited to, when you enter a sweepstakes, contest or promotion sponsored by The Cash4Offers.com and/or when you report a problem with any of our services. Personal information gathered in this way will be used solely for the transaction itself unless otherwise specifically explained at the time the information is collected. The Cash4Offers.com may retain and reference aggregate information about member preferences gathered in these ways.

  4. The Cash4Offers.com utilizes 'cookies' for convenience so that members will not have to log in to the site each time they visit. A cookie is a piece of text that can be entered into the memory of your computer. In this case, it is used to remember your username and password. Most cookies are 'session cookies', meaning that they are automatically deleted at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies, if your browser permits, or to ask your browser to indicate when a cookie is being sent. You can also delete cookie files from your computer at your discretion. Note that if you decline our cookies or ask for notification each time a cookie is being sent, you will need to input your username and password each time you visit The Cash4Offers.com site.

  5. We use your e-mail address to verify your identity and protect against fraud and to contact you when necessary. In addition, our advertisers may choose to occasionally send targeted e-mail to our subscribed members. These direct e-mail messages usually contain some sort of sale, special or promotion that the advertiser is offering. Please note that these messages are sent out on a periodic basis and our advertisers will select a certain segment of our member base to contact based on the demographic profile that they are targeting. If you would not like to receive these periodic e-mails, you may cancel your membership from member control panel.

  6. If a member elects to use our affiliate e-mail to refer a friend, we ask them for the friend's e-mail address. The Cash4Offers.com will send a one-time invitation to visit the site. We do not store the e-mail address after the invitation is sent. The referred friend may contact us with any questions or concerns.

  7. The Cash4Offers.com may share non-personal aggregate, or summary, information regarding its customers with partners or other third parties. Further, we can - and you authorize us to - disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.

  8. The Cash4Offers.com contains links to many web sites. The Cash4Offers.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these web sites.

  9. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, The Cash4Offers.com has used appropriate industry standard procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as firewall, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data. However, no data transmitted over the Internet can be 100% secure.

  10. You must be at least 13 years of age to become a member of The Cash4Offers.com. If you have any questions or concerns about The Cash4Offers.com membership policies, please [contact us](http://www.cash4offers.com/contact.html).

  11. We give users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

    1. You can [log in to the member control panel](http://www.cash4offers.com/login.html) and click the edit info button. There you will be able to change all information you have previously given.

    2. Use our [contact](http://www.cash4offers.com/contact.html) form.

    3. Send mail to the postal address at the bottom of this page.

  12. By registering as a member at The Cash4Offers.com, you agree to accept this privacy policy and are aware that our policy may change from time to time. It is the responsibility of our members to review this policy periodically to ensure that they are aware of our rules and regulations so users are aware of what Personally Identifiable Information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. In the event that a change is made after user registration the user will be notified via e-mail and be given the opportunity to opt-out prior to those changes going into effect. This policy will be available on this page for members to read.

  13. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web Sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

  14. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about our policy, you can contact us or send mail to: 

Cash4Offers  
Ateities 1-40  
Vilnius, LT-08206  
Lithuania 

Phone: +370-600-09470 

Close Window
